webjam.com 2017-06-26

# Webjam - privacypolicy

Webjam Privacy Policy  
Updated April 22, 2009

PRIVACY POLICY 

Your privacy is very important to us. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. If you have additional questions about Webjam general privacy principles, you can contact us at [privacy@webjam.com](http://www.webjam.com/js/tinymce/mail%20to:%20privacy@webjam.com). 

1\.     REGISTRATION

We shall ask you to supply Webjam Registration Data to us when you wish to register as a Member of our website at www.webjam.com in order to aggregate, publish and share Material and/or contribute and participate to a Site run by another Member, for example through user forums or ratings.

2\.     PERSONAL INFORMATION

2.1 The “Webjam Registration Data” that we shall ask you to supply in order to get a Webjam ID shall include  a username, email address, password, gender, date of birth and country of residence; Webjam ID is an account that you create with Webjam to become a Member and use the Webjam Service. You use the username and password portion of your Webjam ID to authenticate with each Site that you operate or contribute to. To each Webjam ID is automatically associated a public profile site that you can operate like any other Site.

2.2 We may also ask you to provide additional personal data to us for particular purposes, such as facilitating the discovery of other Members with related interests and/or backgrounds, communicating with other Members or supplying our products or services to you. In each case it will be your decision as to whether you supply us with the information in question or not and the level of privacy you attach to it, i.e., whether it can be seen by you, just people you have allowed access to that information, or the general public. Together with the Webjam Registration Data, these additional personal data are referred to as the “Webjam Member Data”

2.3 To access, contribute to, or operate another Member’s Site, this Member may ask you to supply additional personal data, referred to as “Site Data”. In the Webjam Terms of Service, Webjam requires each Member to comply with applicable laws and not to use or disclose any of your personal information in a manner that violates this Privacy Policy. 

2.4 Our services are not available to children under 13 and we ask that persons under the age of 13 do not submit any personal information to us. If you are between 13 and 17 years old, you can use this service only in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent or guardian. 

3\.     USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We shall only use your Webjam Registration Data for the following purposes:

3.1    to identify you as a registered user of our website, including any Site that you operate, access or contribute to;

3.2     to provide you with our products and services; 

3.3     to send you information regarding our products and services

3.4    for our own internal purposes in connection with risk control, resolving consumer disputes; and

3.5     for producing statistics and other information relating to our business.

Webjam provides the Member(s) who operates a Site with the ability to collect, store and display some or whole of the Site Data that you may have decided to supply them.

Any information or statistics relating to our business that we disclose to others shall not identify you personally. We may, for example, perform statistical analyses of the behaviour of the users of our website in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site and to inform advertisers as to how many consumers have seen or "clicked" their advertising banners. This information, and any other general information about our users that we share with advertisers and other partners, will not disclose personal information about you.

4\.     DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We shall only disclose your Registration Data to other people in the following circumstances:

 4.1    to prepare or send any communications to you, or to assist us in connection with any of our administrative or business functions, or in the provision of any of our products or our services to you; 

4.2     if we are asked to do so by any legal or regulatory authority, or if we believe that it would be proper to do so in connection with any legal or regulatory matter. 

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with:  
·    Service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf;  
·    Other businesses with which we partner or which we carefully select to offer you products, services, and promotions through our website or offline; and  
·    Other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users.   
Unless they are already legally bound to keep your Registration Data confidential, we shall enter into agreements with anyone to whom we disclose your Registration Data under points 4.1 and 4.2 obliging them to keep your Registration Data confidential.

Webjam does not share personal information with third parties except in the circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. However any information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the Webjam Service, including on any Site, becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by Members, Webjam or others without restriction.

5.    Ratings

Members can choose to rate, review and comment upon, quantitatively and qualitatively any of the Materials, and/or to trust other members. As an unregistered Visitor, we may allow you to rate some Material. Your review ratings and trust statements may be displayed publicly unless you change the default configuration; your Member name is automatically displayed with reviews and comments you publish, and if other Members choose to, they can receive email notifications of your publications or publish their own comments to your reviews or any Material you might create. 

We, and our licensees, can republish your Material with the related ratings, reviews and comments as described in the User Terms and Conditions. We may publish ratings and use them to develop aggregate ratings, personalize site views, adverts served and merchandise products. We use your review ratings and network of trusted Members to personalise site views and identify and possibly feature popular Members or reputable Materials.. We may also use ratings by Members to identify Materials detrimental to the community. Whilst we don't expect to transfer the complete review rating and web of trust database to others (except as contemplated elsewhere in this statement), we use the database throughout our networks and to generate results for others.

6\.     SALE AND SUPPLY

We shall comply with the following restrictions in relation to your personal information.

6.1     we shall not sell your Registration Data to anyone else; and

6.2     subject to the exceptions in points 4.1 and 4.2, we shall not supply your Registration Data to anyone else so that they can use it for their own purposes.

7\.     SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We shall take reasonable steps to ensure that your Registration Data are kept secure whilst it is in our possession.   
We shall not store your financial data and we use your financial data only for the processing of your purchase of additional Webjam Services we may offer you

8\.     OTHER INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

When you visit our site we may log IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. 

We may collect information about your viewing habits when you visit our website through your IP address and by using cookies and other web tools in the following ways.

8.1    COOKIES. A "cookie" is a small electronic file that collects information when someone visits a website. A cookie can identify the pages that are being viewed, and this can assist us to select the pages that the viewer sees. Some cookies only exist whilst viewers are online, but "persistent" cookies - which are not session-based - remain on the viewer's computer, so that he or she can be recognised as a previous visitor when he or she next visits our website. This information allows us to collect information about a viewer's browsing habits whilst on our site, and this can be useful in assisting us to monitor and improve our services.

We do not store sensitive information such as account numbers or passwords in "persistent" cookies, and cookies, in themselves, do not contain enough information to identify you. You will only acquire a personal identity in relation to your browsing habits after you have formally provided us with your Registration Data for the purposes outlined in point 3 above. 

8.2    GIF AND OTHER WEB TOOLS. In addition to using cookies, we might also use GIFs and other web tools to collect information about your browsing activities whilst on our site. In this respect the information that is provided is similar to the information supplied by cookies, and we use it for the same purposes.

Any information that we acquire about you using cookies, GIFs or other web tools is subject to the same restrictions and conditions as any other Registration Data we collect about you.

NOTE: We use an advertising server to display advertisements on our website. Some of those advertisements may contain cookies, GIFs, or other web tools that are set by other people such as advertising agencies, or the businesses to which the advertisements in question relate. We do not have access to any information that might be collected in this way, and, if you are concerned, you should contact the advertiser for more information.

9\.     AMENDMENTS, CANCELLATION, AND CONTACT US

You may amend your Registration Data which you have supplied to us by visiting your “Edit Profile” page. If you wish your Registration Data to be removed from our database you should do so by going to “delete my account” on the “personal details tab” of your profile.  You shall be deemed to have cancelled any contract or licence you may have had with us to which the Registration Data in question applied, and (as we shall not have been at fault in those circumstances) you shall not be entitled to any compensation or refunds in relation to the cancellation of the applicable contract or licence. 

Please contact us at [privacy@webjam.com](http://www.webjam.com/js/tinymce/mail%20to:%20privacy@webjam.com) in relation to the matters to which this point 9 relates, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy has been prepared to meet the requirements of the UK's Data Protection Act 1998, and it only relates to the collection, protection, disclosure and use of personal data belonging to living individuals. It does not relate to data which emanate from companies or other entities, although the general principles regarding our collection and use of data is broadly the same irrespective of  whoever is the user of our website, or our customer.
